[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Do you remember bumping me for Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm a British gentleman.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "I thought about that, because I thought you might ask me that, because I think it's a really good question.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "If you could relive five minutes of your life, which would they be?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "Well, initially, the idea was -- I'd do a show back in the UK called \"Life Stories,\" which is a more auto-biographical hour- long interview with one guest.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "So let's start by letting everybody know how this show came to be because initially, you weren't supposed to be a live breaking news show, correct?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I was desperate and she listened to this desperate pathetic little Brit, and thought come, come to Chicago.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Are you sure you didn't invite yourself to be on Oprah's show?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, look, I mean -- I have spent my life back in Britain as a journalist involved with breaking news.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How did you feel about it?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Did you watch your own interviews?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "We don't want to see this stark Mediavalism that represses women, that crushes the rights of people, that rolls us back a millennium, that fosters violence and does everything that we abhor that it would take over.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What is your nightmare scenario for you?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I found him incredibly impressive.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "OK, and what did you think of your performance?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I did like him.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Did you like him?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Colin Powell is a remarkable man.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What about Colin Powell?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, I do now.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "You don't know what gumbo is?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, it is your thing.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Why can't it be my thing, too?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "-- seems a little shallow to me.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Some of them were impressive people I've met actually turned out not to run for president which I thought was a shame.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "So where would you like to begin?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Are you a fan?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Has he disappointed, you Obama?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I'm still rooting for the black president.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "How's he doing, the half white guy?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "That is a tough question.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "She's German and a supermodel.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Why shouldn't I ask Heidi Klum?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Well, are you American yet?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, I guess you could ask her but it just seems like an odd choice to ask somebody --", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "But she's an American citizen, why shouldn't I ask her?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "ORGAN: It was a joy for Anderson.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "When you were covering the royal wedding, how painful was it to sit next to Anderson Cooper for that many hours?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "You are.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Am I now doing the Tebow?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I haven't yet but the invitation remains extended to William and Kate.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Now have you had them on the show yet?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Kim was on the show?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, actually it was a week before we taped it because it coincided with her book launch.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "So does that kind of thing piss you off?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "My last.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Your second?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Are you auditioning?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Are we done?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Are you under the influence right now of any substances?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Do you remember bumping me for Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "I like Charlie Sheen.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "So why were you so nice to him?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Do you think he was high, though, while you were interviewing him?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, I think you're absolutely right on that -- on that point.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What is this problem here?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not in the 1 percent, no, but I am --", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "You're in the 1 percent, right?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you know the answers?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What are you worth?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Just, they can.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "In the graceful, brilliant way he did with every situation for 25 years, one of my heroes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How do you think Larry King would have handled the situation, like any of those?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes, he genuinely was.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Is he one of your heroes?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "It's always challenging.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "How do you feel when you have to interview somebody like that?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "My God.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Do you think Barbara Walters is feisty?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Oh, you did not -- I'll throw this mic pack at your --", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Once, and I remain there.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "No, you had Oprah.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Not bad, was it?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Certainly one of them, yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Was she your most impressive guest that you have had?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Probably the biggest, right?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "So, how many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I have been known to.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Do you talk about that?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "That would also be an --", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "And your previous wife?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How many others were there?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I thought about that because I thought you might ask me that, because I think it's a really good question.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "If you could relive five minute of your life, which would they be?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "See how easy it is?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I would relive the moment they announced that we won newspaper of the year.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "So what would you want to relive from that?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Because it was long-winded and you really didn't say much.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "If you could walk through that door again, would you?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Yes, I absolutely agree with you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "We're going to get into that when we come back.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "What can I say?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "You tell us.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Does sex get better with age, do you think?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "It's about good interview technique.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "So what's that about?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I liked him.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "A lot of comedians are quite depressive, tricky characters.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Females or male comedians?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Well a completely mad woman doing a completely mad thing on live television, and one of the most dangerous moments of my life.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "What about Kathy Griffin, when she crawled over the desk and tried to face hump you?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "No, I can't.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Can you imagine sitting here and Kathy Griffin comes at you like a rampant hyena?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "It was -- I had to fend her off, like I did you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "How did you defend yourself?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "You know, only God knows.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Can we expect the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "Would you mind asking him to tell me?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "I don't remember when I joined.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "When did you join, first of all?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "One year.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 799, "question": "How long have you bee on?", "qSentId": 798}, {"answer": "No, but I keep saying on the show, hoping that he's sitting there watching, thinking to himself, if I just do one interview with one guy on TV, it's going to be this guy.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "Have you reached out to him?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "I do interviews in a different way than anyone else.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "What do you have to offer him that everybody else doesn't?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "You obviously love it, because you keep coming back.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "What if he doesn't like it?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "He will like it, because he's my hero.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "What if he doesn't like it?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "Is that the life you wish you could lead?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "Being here with you, Piers.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "What he your idea of a little bit of heaven?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "To play you.", "docId": "120116pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "What's the big dream role for you?", "qSentId": 861}]